（梅西百貨感恩節遊行）
Hey, hon? Would you help me get the plates down?
親愛的，你可以幫我把盤子拿下來嗎？
Hey, here's an idea. Why don't we use our wedding china today?
嘿，我有個主意 我們今天用我們的結婚瓷盤好不好？
Or we could save them for a fancy special occasion.
或者我們可以等到很特別的場合再用
How about this: You could treat me like I'm an equal..
可不可以這樣： 你要不就平等對待我…
or talk down to me like I'm a child.
要不就把我當成小孩對我說話
No, I just think we should save our china for something really special.
不，我只是認為我們應該把瓷盤留到 真正特別的場合使用
Like if the queen of England comes over.
像是英國女皇來訪的時候
Honey, she keeps canceling on us. Take the hint.
親愛的，她一直取消跟我們的約 你還不懂那是什麼意思嗎？
What if something breaks? They're expensive.
打破了怎麼辦呢？它們可是很貴的
What is the point of having them if we never use them?
東西擺著不用的意義何在呢？
Okay. But if something breaks and then the queen comes over..
好吧，但是如果打破了 然後女王又要來訪…
- I will explain it to her. - Like I'd let you talk to the queen.
-我會跟她解釋 -你以為我會讓你跟她說話啊
Wow, the parade is really good this year.
哇，今年的遊行真是棒
Man, those horses can crap.
天啊，那些馬還真能拉屎
Next up is a marching band from Muskogee, Oklahoma.
下一個遊行隊伍是來自 奧克拉荷馬州的馬斯科吉
Muskogee? That's like four hours from Tulsa!
馬斯科吉？離土爾沙才四小時車程！
Y'all look great!
你全看起來棒透了！
That's right, I said "y'all!"
沒錯，我是說「你全」
Here's the float with the stars of the popular daytime soap..
接下來是日間肥皂劇…
Days of Our Lives.
《我們的日子》的眾星們
Oh, my God!
喔，我的天！
Aren't you one of the stars of the popular daytime soap Days of our Lives?
你不是日間肥皂劇 《我們的日子》眾星之一嗎？
I forgot! I'm supposed to be there!
我忘了！我應該要參加遊行的！
I can't believe I forgot! I usually write stuff like this down on my arm!
我不敢相信我忘了！ 我通常會寫在手臂上的！
Stupid long sleeves!
爛長袖衣服！
- What are you gonna do? - I'll come up with a good reason..
-你要怎麼辦呢？ -我得找個好借口說明…
why I wasn't there.
我為什麼沒有到
The producers are gonna be mad. They sat us down and said:
製作人一定會很生氣 他們昨天把我們全都叫進去然後說：
"Everyone has to be there,6 a.m. sharp. That means you, Tribbiani."
「大家都要在早上六點整到 尤其是你，崔比亞尼」
Like I was some kind of idiot.
好像我是什麼笨蛋似的
Well, you proved them wrong.
嗯，你剛好證明了他們是錯的
The One With Rachels Other Sister
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Oh, Emma.
喔，艾□
This is your first Thanksgiving.
這是你第一個感恩節
What are you thankful for?
你要感謝什麼呢？
Mommy's boobies?
媽咪的胸部嗎？
A lot of people are thankful for those.
很多人都會感謝那東西的
Hello? Rachel?
哈囉？瑞秋？
Who is it?
是誰？
It's your favorite sister.
是你最喜歡的妹妹
- Jill? - Amy!
-吉兒？ -艾美！
Hide my rings.
把我的戒指藏起來
Amy! Happy Thanksgiving.
艾美！感恩節快樂
Do you have a hair straightener?
你有沒有直髮器呢？
Hi.
嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
-嗨 -嗨
Hair straightener.
直髮器
- I haven't seen you in, like, a year. - I know. I know. I've just been crazed.
-我好像一年沒有見到你了 -我知道，我知道，我忙翻了
Well, me too. I had a baby.
喔，我也是，我生了小孩
I decorated Dad's office.
我把爸的辦公室重新裝潢了一次
Yeah? Well, unless you pushed a desk out of your vagina, not the same thing.
是嗎？除非你有把桌子從陰道擠出去 否則那可是不同的事
About that hair straightener, honey, I really need one.
關於直髮器的事 親愛的，我真的需要
I'm gonna have dinner at my boyfriend's house.
我要到我男朋友家用晚餐
Oh, my God.
喔，我的天
Is this Emmett?
這是愛門嗎？
It's Emma.
是艾□
It's a girl?
是個女生？
- Hey, Amy. - Amy, you remember Ross?
-嗨，艾美 -艾美，你記得羅斯吧？
Not really.
不太記得
But you are much cuter than that geeky guy she used to date.
但是你比她之前的呆頭鵝男友可愛多了
That was me.
那個人就是我
No, he was this creepy guy from high school who had this huge crush on her..
不，他是高中時代的怪男生 從好像是九年級…
since, like, the ninth grade.
就很喜歡她的
Still me.
那還是我
No, I'm not talking about you.
不，我不是在說你
It was your fat friend's brother with that bad Afro.
那是你那個胖朋友的哥哥 留著可笑的黑人頭
Okay, Amy, I'm gonna save you some time, okay? All me!
好了，艾美，讓我節省你的時間 都是我！
Careful. Careful.
小心，小心
Careful!
小心！
I'll tell you what. For the rest of our lives..
這樣子好了 我們這一輩子…
I'll be careful until told otherwise.
我都會很小心，除非你要我做別的
- This isn't the china we picked out. - I know.
-這不是我們選的瓷盤 -我知道
After you left the store, I chose different ones.
在你離開店裡之後，我選了別的
- Why? - Your taste is a little feminine for me.
-為什麼？ -你的品味對我而言太女性化了
Suddenly flowers are feminine?
花朵什麼時候變成女性化的象徵了？
Hey, everybody! Happy Thanksgiving!
嘿，大家好！感恩節快樂！
- Happy Thanksgiving. Phoebe! - What's going on, Joe?
-感恩節快樂，菲比 -怎麼了，喬伊？
Listen, I need a good lie.
聽著，我需要編個天衣無縫的謊
Okay.
好的
How about the whole "man walking on the moon" thing, you know?
「人類走在月球上」那個謊言如何？
You can see the strings, people!
根本就可以看到線，真是的！
No, no, no. I need a good lie to explain why I wasn't at a work thing today.
不，不，我需要一個謊言來解釋 為什麼我今天錯過了一件工作的事
- Honey, you stink at lying. - I do not.
-親愛的，你根本不會說謊 -我會的
Really? Let me ask you something. Yesterday at the coffeehouse..
真的？讓我問你 昨天發生在咖啡屋的事…
I went to the bathroom. When I came back, my muffin was gone. Who took it?
我去上廁所，回來的時候我的鬆餅 就不見了，是誰拿走的？
Somebody opened the door to the coffeehouse..
有人打開咖啡屋的大門…
and a raccoon ran in and went straight for your muffin. I said:
然後一隻浣熊就跑進來 直接拿走你的鬆餅，我說：
"Hey, don't eat that! That's Phoebe's!" And he said..
「嘿，不能吃！那是菲比的！」 然後他說…
He said, "Joey, you stink at lying." What am I gonna do?
他說「喬伊，你根本不會說謊」 我該怎麼辦呢？
Don't worry. We'll come up with a lie. I'll help you.
別擔心，我們會想個謊的 我會幫你的
- Great. That'd be great. Thank you. - Sure. What was the work thing?
-太好了，太棒了，謝謝你 -沒問題，你錯過了什麼工作的事？
- "Pick up Grandma at the airport." - Oh, man!
-「到機場接奶奶」 -喔，天啊！
She's precious.
她真是我的心肝寶貝
Do you ever worry that she's gonna get your real nose?
你會不會擔心 她會遺傳到你真正的鼻子？
Amy..
艾美…
Yes, I do. I really do.
是的，我會，我真的會
Hello?
喂？
Yeah, hang on, one sec. Can I take this upstairs?
是，等一下 我可以到樓上講嗎？
Sure. We don't live there, but..
當然，我們不住在樓上，但是…
Seriously? It's just these rooms?
真的嗎？只有這幾間房間？
- I thought you were a doctor. - Yeah. No, Ross has a Ph.D.
-我以為你是醫生 -不，羅斯有博士學位
God, she is unbelievable.
天啊，她真是不可思議
I know. I mean, a Ph.D. is just as good as an MD.
對啊，博士學位就跟醫學學位一樣好啊
Sure, Ross, yeah!
是喔，羅斯，對啊！
If I have a heart attack at a restaurant, I want you there with your fossil brush.
如果我在餐廳時心臟病發 我會希望你跟你的化石刷子就在一旁
- Stupid Thanksgiving. - What?
-愚蠢的感恩節 -怎麼了？
- What? What happened? - My boyfriend canceled on me.
-怎麼了？發生什麼事？ -我男朋友跟我取消約會了
I mean, I finally find a real relationship.
我好不容易才找到一段真感情
Someone that I can spend this day with, and then his wife comes back into town!
一個可以跟我共渡今天的人 然後他老婆竟然回來了！
I swear, it's almost not even worth dating married guys.
我發誓 跟已婚男人約會真是不值得
Don't say that.
別這樣說
God, I was so looking forward to this.
天啊，我本來很期待今天的
It was gonna be such a beautiful Thanksgiving.
本來會是很美好的感恩節的
We were gonna have sushi.
我們本來要吃壽司的
Amy, don't cry.
艾美，別哭
- Ross, can I talk to you in private? - Sure, you wanna go upstairs, or..?
-羅斯，我可以私下跟你談談嗎？ -當然，你想要去樓上或是…？
Look, I was thinking, if it's okay with Monica..
聽著，我想如果摩妮卡不介意的話…
I would like to invite Amy to Thanksgiving.
我想要邀請艾美跟我們共度感恩節
I think that's a great idea. It'll be like the Pilgrims bringing the Indians syphilis.
我認為這是個好主意，就像清教徒 把梅毒帶來美國給印地安人一樣
Look, I know she's a little tough to take.
聽著，我知道她有點難搞
But she has nowhere else to go, and she's my sister. She's Emma's aunt.
但是她沒有其他地方可以去了 而且她是我妹妹，是艾□的阿姨
- And I would like them to bond. - I don't want them bonding too much.
-而我想要讓她們相處融洽 -我不想要她們相處太融洽
I don't want her telling Emma she needs a nose job.
我不要她告訴艾□說 她需要整形
Ross, she may need one. We're just gonna have to make our peace with that!
羅斯，她很可能會需要的 我們也只能接受了！
Amy..
艾美…
Amy?
艾美？
Amy!
艾美！
I'm out in the hall.
我在外面
Your baby had some sort of explosion of stink.
你們的嬰兒好像爆發出一股臭氣
The bonding's going great.
相處的可真融洽
- Hi! - Hey.
-嗨 -嘿
Hey, you guys. This is my sister, Amy.
嘿，大夥兒，這是我妹妹艾美
This is Chandler, Joey, Phoebe, and you know Mon.
這是錢德、喬伊、菲比 還有你認識的摩妮卡
Oh, my God.
喔，我的天
You're on Days of Our Lives!
你有演《我們的日子》
Yeah.
是的
Wow! They must put a lot of makeup on you.
哇！他們一定是幫你化很濃的妝
Happy Thanksgiving.
感恩節快樂
- Hey. - Hi.
-嘿 -嗨
So welcome. Is this the first time you're seeing Emma?
歡迎，這是你第一次見到艾□嗎？
Yeah, I think so. It's nice to meet you, Emma.
是的，我想是的 很高興認識你，艾□
- Phoebe. - That's a funny noise.
-菲比 -那聲音真好玩
- Phoebe? I still need some help here. - Right. Okay.
-菲比？我還需要你幫我 -好的
So it's not just the lie you tell, but it's the way you tell it. For example..
不止是你說的謊言本身 你說的方式也很重要，例如…
if you look at the ground when you talk, people know you're lying.
如果你說的時候看著地上 人們就知道你在說謊
I don't know why this is so hard for me. Lying is basically just acting..
我不知道為什麼這對我如此困難 說謊基本上就跟演戲一樣
- and I am a terrific actor. - You are a terrific actor.
-而我可是演技精湛的演員 -你是演技精湛的演員
I could talk to the producers for you. I'm a great liar.
我可以幫你跟製作人說 我可是說謊高手
Take Monica's dress. I said I loved it.
舉摩妮卡的衣服當例子，我說我很喜歡
- I hate it. - Hey!
-事實上我討厭極了 -嘿！
I'm also a great moron.
我同時也是白癡高手
- Hey. Where's the baby? - We just put her down for a nap.
-嘿，嬰兒在哪裡呢？ -我們剛把她抱去睡了
Listen, I was just thinking. You know what would be incredible?
聽著，我剛剛在想 你們知道什麼事會很棒嗎？
If you guys died!
就是如果你們死了！
Thank you, Amy.
謝謝你，艾美
No, no, then I would get the baby.
然後我就可以得到嬰兒
It would be just like a movie. At first I wouldn't know what to do with her.
就像是電影情節一樣 剛開始我會全無頭緒
And then I would rise to the occasion. Then I'd get a makeover and get married.
然後時機來臨時 我會完全改變，然後結婚去
That's a great movie!
很棒的電影！
Now, listen, not that you guys could stop me or anything..
反正你們也不能阻止我…
because you know, you'd be dead.
因為你們已經死了
But I was thinking about changing her name.
但是我想要幫她改名字
I'm just not really a big fan of Emily.
我就是不大喜歡艾蜜莉
Emma.
艾□
Emma? Ross wants you.
艾□？羅斯在叫你
Phoebe!
菲比！
Why does she keep making that noise?
她為什麼一直發出那種怪聲呢？
Honey, I don't know how to tell you this..
親愛的，我不知道要如何告訴你
but if something were to happen to Ross or myself..
但是如果我跟羅斯發生了什麼事
- you wouldn't get the baby. - Well, who would?
-你不會得到嬰兒的 -那，誰會呢？
Well, we haven't officially asked them yet..
嗯，我們還沒有正式問過他們
but we would want Monica and Chandler.
但是我們會希望是摩妮卡跟錢德
- Who? - You're in their apartment.
-誰？ -我們正在他們的公寓裡
I can't believe you'd want us to raise Emma.
我不敢相信你們要我們撫養艾□
Oh, my God, I'm so moved.
喔，我的天，我真是太感動了
I don't believe this. Hold on a second. You guys die..
我不敢相信，等一下 你們死了…
and I don't get your baby?
然後嬰兒不是我的？
Amy, see, we're a lot closer to Monica and Chandler.
艾美，我們跟摩妮卡跟錢德比較親近
We see them every day. And truthfully, you don't seem connected to the baby.
我們每天都見面，而且老實說 你好像也不太親近嬰兒
Connected? To what? She's a lump.
親近？親近什麼？ 她只是一堆肉
You know, guys, I've gotta say this means so much to me.
我必須要跟你們說 這對我意義重大
I mean, that you would trust me with your child.
我是說，你們肯相信我 托負你們的孩子給我
I mean, we all know that Monica and I have been..
大家都知道摩妮卡跟我一直試著…
trying to have a baby of our own.
想要生小孩
You know, I've had my doubts about my skills as a father, but..
我也有懷疑過 自己當父親的能力，但是…
That you two..
你們兩個…
- That you two.. - This guy?
-你們兩個… -這個人嗎？
Seriously?
真的嗎？
Okay, it's time for dinner.
好了，晚餐時間到了
Everyone, we're using our fancy china..
各位，我們將使用我們的精緻瓷盤…
and it's very expensive, so please be careful.
它們是很貴的，所以請小心
Okay, just to be clear, comedy with the plates will not be well-received.
好了，再說明一次 不要拿這些盤子開玩笑
Hey!
嘿
How come my plate's less fancy than everyone else's?
為什麼我的盤子不如別人的精緻？
Do you not trust me with a fancy plate?
你不信任我 不讓我用你的精緻餐盤嗎？
No, honey. That's a special plate.
不，親愛的，那是特別的盤子
See, it's a game. Whoever gets that plate wins.
這是一個遊戲 拿到那盤子的人就是贏家
I can't believe I won!
我不敢相信我贏了！
You know, this is such a slap in the face. I mean, I'm your sister..
這真的很侮辱，我是你妹妹…
and you would give your baby to these strangers over me.
你卻可以把嬰兒給這些陌生人而不給我
Monica is Ross' sister.
摩妮卡是羅斯的妹妹
No, Ross' sister was really fat.
不，羅斯的妹妹很胖的
That was me.
那就是我
No, she was this dorky girl in school who followed Rachel around like a puppy..
不，她是個蠢蠢的女生 在學校時就像小狗一樣跟著瑞秋
Amy, you've got to stop doing that!
艾美，我不許你再這樣了！
Okay, listen, I know you're having a bit of a family crisis..
好了，我知道你現在正在經歷家庭危機
but you don't have to take it out on the plates.
但是你不需要把氣出在盤子身上
I mean, in fact, I think that everyone..
其實我認為每個人…
should cut their food like this:
都應該這樣切食物
Now, see? This way, you protect the plates..
現在，看到了嗎？ 這樣不只可以保護盤子…
and let's face it, you have fun.
而且還挺好玩的
Okay, how about this? If you guys die..
好吧，要是這樣呢？ 如果你們死了…
and the crazy plate lady dies..
而且瘋狂盤子女士也死了…
- then do I get the baby? - No, if crazy plate lady..
-那我可以得到嬰兒嗎？ -不，如果瘋狂盤子女士…
If Monica dies, then I would get Emma. Right?
如果摩妮卡死了 那艾□就是我的了，對嗎？
- Well, actually.. - Actually what?
-嗯，其實… -怎樣？
It's just.. It's just that in that case..
只是… 如果是那樣的話…
then Emma would go to my parents.
那艾□就會去跟我父母親住
- What? - Hurts, doesn't it?
-什麼？ -很傷你的心，對不對？
Who has to die for me to get her?
我要等誰死了才能得到她？
So if Monica's not around, I'm not good enough to raise Emma?
所以如果摩妮卡不在了 我就沒有資格撫養艾□了？
No, that is not what we're saying.
不，我們不是這個意思
Yeah, he's lying. He looked down.
他在說謊，他看了地上
Well, what's wrong with me? Am I incompetent?
那我有什麼不好的呢？我無能嗎？
Because I managed to survive whatever it is that killed the three of you!
因為無論是什麼東西殺了你們三個 我都存活了下來！
You're taking this the wrong way. We think you are going to be a wonderful parent.
你反應過度了 我們認為你會是很好的父親
It's just.. You're more the, you know, fun parent.
只是…你是比較風趣的父親
Yeah, and we wanna make sure Emma also has someone like Monica..
是的，我們想要確定艾□也有像 摩妮卡這樣的人照顧
who's more of a disciplinarian.
比較有紀律的人
Someone who can be firm and strict.
比較堅定嚴格的人
That's not how you see me, is it?
你們對我的感覺不是真的那樣吧？
No, you're all about the fun.
不，你真的很好玩
I may not know a lot about babies, but do you really think I'm not capable?
我或許不是很瞭解嬰兒 但是你們真的認為我沒有能力嗎？
No. You both are equally capable.
不，你們兩個能力相當
It's just you're strongest when you're together.
只不過你們在一起的時候是最強的
Okay. So if we both had Emma, and I died..
好的，如果我們有艾□，然後我死了…
she'd have to give her up.
她也不能擁有她
Sure. Monica would have to give her up.
當然，摩妮卡也必須把她讓出來
I lie better than that, right?
我說謊說的至少比他好，對吧？
Let me just get this straight. So my two friends die, I get Emma.
讓我搞清楚，如果我的兩個朋友死了 我得到艾□
Then my wife dies. Then Emma, the one tiny ray of hope left in my life..
然後我老婆死了，那我生命中剩下的 唯一一小塊希望，艾□…
- gets taken away from me? - There's your movie.
-也會從我身邊被帶走？ -演的好精采哦
Hey, there you are.
嘿，你在這裡
- You disappeared after dinner. - Did somebody miss me?
-你在晚餐之後就消失了 -有人想念我嗎？
Was there a child to raise poorly?
有嬰兒需要被無能的父親撫養長大嗎？
Ross and Rachel don't know what they're saying.
羅斯跟瑞秋根本什麼都不懂
It's not like they're so responsible.
他們自己也不是多有責任感
Emma is a product of a bottle of merlot and a five-year-old condom.
艾□只不過是一瓶紅酒 跟一個過期保險套的產品
No, but they're right. I'm not a strong father figure, and I never will be.
不，他們是對的，我不是強悍的父親 我永遠都不會是
No, you learn these things. You grow into it.
不，這些是要學習的 你會逐漸學會的
Yeah, but it's not who I am.
是的，但那就不是我了
Everything they said is exactly why I was worried about having a kid. And it's true.
他們說的一切，都是我擔心有小孩之後 會面對的問題，是真的
- And look, everybody knows it. - I don't know it.
-而且，大家都知道 -我並不知道
I wanna have a kid with you because I think you'll be an amazing dad.
我要跟你生小孩因為我認為 你會是很棒的父親
At the fun parts and at the hard parts.
不管是風趣還是有紀律
Well, can you picture me saying, "Go to your room, you're grounded"?
那你可以想像我說 「回房去，你被禁足了」嗎？
Can you hear me say, "You're grounded"?
你可以想像我說「你被禁足了」嗎？
You said that to me last week.
你上星期才那樣對我說
How hard is it? "No shoes on the furniture!"
我叫你不要穿著鞋子踏在傢俱上 到底有多難呢？
The producer from Days left a message asking why I wasn't at the parade.
製作人剛剛留言 問我為什麼沒有參加遊行
They said everybody's really pissed off at me. And they all got to meet Santa!
他說大家都對我很不爽 而且他們都有見到聖誕老公公！
It's okay. I thought of the perfect lie for you.
沒關係，我幫你想了一個完美謊言
It's easy to remember, and it doesn't invite a lot of questions.
很容易記，而且不會引來更多的問題
Does it have something to do with a spaceship?
是跟太空船有關的嗎？
The Statue of Liberty came to life..
自由女神活了過來…
You weren't at the parade because you had a family emergency.
你沒有參加遊行 因為家裡出了緊急狀況
I like that! Yeah!
我喜歡！耶！
I wasn't at the parade because I had a family emergency.
我沒有參加遊行 因為家裡出了緊急狀況
What happened?
發生什麼事？
- My sister's raccoon came.. - No, nothing with a raccoon!
-我姐的浣熊… -不，別提浣熊！
- Wait, what are you doing? - Setting the table.
-等等，你們在做什麼？ -擺餐具
We thought it might be nice to use the fancy china for dessert too.
我們覺得用這些精緻餐盤來吃甜點 應該也很不錯
How nice. Maybe later we can all go blow our noses on my wedding dress.
很不錯，或許等一下我們可以 去拿我的結婚禮服來擤鼻涕
Hey, dude, you okay? Sorry about before.
嘿，兄弟，你還好嗎？ 剛剛的事我很抱歉
That's okay. You're totally right. I don't know anything about disciplining a child.
沒關係，你完全是對的 我根本就不知道如何管教孩子
But it did hurt my feelings, and I want you to know that if I die..
但是我還是很傷心 而且我要你知道，如果我死了…
you don't get Joey.
你別想得到喬伊
In case you hadn't noticed, I'm not talking to you.
如果你還沒注意到 我現在不會跟你說話的
You know, this is just.. This is classic Rachel.
真的是… 這是典型的瑞秋
Oh, yeah, right. Remember in high school when I died and didn't give you my baby?
喔，對喔，記得在高中我死的時候 也沒有把我的嬰兒給你嗎？
This might be my one chance to have a child, Rachel.
這或許是我唯一擁有小孩的機會，瑞秋
I mean, you know that I have been so busy focusing on my career..
你知道我一直忙於我的事業…
- What career? - I'm a decorator.
-什麼事業？ -我是室內設計師
You decorate Dad's office and now you're a decorator?
你裝潢了爸的辦公室 就是設計師了嗎？
Okay, I went to the zoo yesterday, now I'm a koala bear.
好的，我昨天去了動物園 現在我就是無尾熊了
- Why can't you ever be supportive? - You wanna talk supportive?
-你為什麼不能多支持我一點？ -你要談支持嗎？
You didn't come and visit me when I was in the hospital having the baby!
我在醫院生小孩時你可沒有來看過我！
You didn't come see me in the hospital when I was getting my lips done!
我在醫院整形嘴唇時你也沒有來看我！
I did the first time.
我第一次有去
You know what? You wanna know why I am not giving Emily to you?
你想知道我為什麼不要 把艾蜜莉給你嗎？
- Emma. - Whose side are you on?!
-是艾□ -你是站誰那邊的？
I'm not giving you Emma because you can't handle the responsibility of a child.
我不給你艾□，是因為你無法扛起 照顧小孩子的責任
Well, how hard could it be? You do it.
那有多難呢？你都做得到
You wanna know why you don't want me to have the baby?
你知道，你為什麼 不想讓我得到嬰兒嗎？
Because you don't want me to be happy.
因為你不想看到我快樂
- You have always been jealous of me. - Jealous of what?
-你總是在忌妒我 -忌妒你什麼？
Of your lack of responsibility? Your immaturity?
忌妒你沒有責任感嗎？ 還是你的不成熟？
Your total disregard for other people's feelings?
你那種完全忽略別人感受的作為嗎？
To name a few.
這只是其中幾項
You've always been like this.
你總是這樣
You had to have everything, and I couldn't have anything.
你總是要所有的東西 而我什麼都得不到
Like in junior high, when you stole Timmy from me.
就像在國中的時候 你搶走我的提米
I mean, do you even realize how much that hurt me?
你知道那傷我有多深嗎？
Timmy was my boyfriend, and you made out with him!
提米是我的男朋友 而你跟他偷親熱！
Come on, that was 20 years ago. Get over it.
別這樣，那已經是二十年前的事了 別太記恨
I cannot believe that I invited you here today!
我不敢相信我在今天邀請了你
Yeah, well, you know what I cannot believe? That my so-called sister..
是喔，你知道我不能相信什麼嗎？ 我所謂的姐姐…
gets a 30 percent discount from Ralph Lauren, and I still have to pay retail?
有洛夫羅倫七折的折扣優惠 而我卻要付零售價
It's 45.
是五五折
You bitch.
你這個賤人
You just think you're so perfect..
你就是認為你很完美…
with your new baby and your small apartment.
擁有你的新生兒 還有你的小公寓
Well, let me tell you something. Your baby isn't even that cute.
讓我告訴你一件事 你的嬰兒並不怎麼可愛
Too far, Amy. Too far.
太過分了，艾美，太過分了
- You take that back. - No.
-你收回那句話 -不
- Take it back! - No. What are you gonna do? Make me?
-收回那句話！ -不，你能怎樣呢？強迫我嗎？
Hey, man, I work out!
嘿，我有上健身房！
- So do I. - I do Pilates.
-我也有 -我有做普拉提
- I do yoga. - Bring it on!
-我有做瑜伽 -放馬過來！
Put the plates in the boxes! Put the plates in the boxes!
盤子放到箱子裡！ 盤子放到箱子裡！
- Did you just push me? - Yeah, I think I did.
-你剛剛推了我嗎？ -是的，沒錯
All right, that's it.
好了，夠了
Forget the bubble wrap! There isn't time!
別管泡泡包裝了！沒有時間了！
Frizzy, frizzy, frizzy!
卷，卷，卷！
- Shouldn't we stop this? - Are you out of your mind?
-我們應該阻止她們嗎？ -你瘋了嗎？
Let's throw some Jell-O on them!
我們應該倒一些果凍到她們身上！
Hey, someone could get hurt.
嘿，有人會受傷的
Kick her, Rach! Kick her!
踢她，瑞秋！踢她！
Pull her top off, Rach! Pull her top off!
把她上衣脫掉，瑞秋！ 把她上衣脫掉
Gross!
噁心！
All right, that is it! This is our apartment, and you cannot behave this way!
好了，到此為止，這是我們家 你們不可以有這種行為！
If you can't act your age, you shouldn't be here at all.
如果你們不能表現得像成人 你們就不應該在這裡
Those plates may not be as nice as the pretty pink ones that I picked out..
那些瓷盤或許沒有像我挑的那些 粉紅色瓷盤好看…
but they're important to Monica. And I want you to apologize to her, now.
但是它們對摩妮卡很重要 而我要你們現在就跟她道歉
- I'm sorry. - Mon, I'm so sorry.
-我很抱歉 -摩妮卡，我很抱歉
Okay. That's better.
好了，這樣好多了
Now, I want you to apologize to each other and mean it.
現在，我要你們誠心地跟彼此道歉
- Sorry. - Sorry.
-對不起 -對不起
By the way, that fight was totally arousing.
對了，剛才那場架真是讓人情慾高漲
Dude, well done.
幹的好
If I die and Rachel dies and Monica dies, you can totally take care of Emma.
如果我跟瑞秋還有摩妮卡死了 你可以照顧艾□
Yeah? Well, thanks.
是嗎？謝謝
So.. So now do I get Joey?
那… 那我可以得到喬伊嗎？
Okay. But you should know he eats a lot and shoves pennies up his nose.
好的，但是你得知道他一天吃五餐 而且還會塞硬幣到鼻孔裡
Are you okay, Mon?
你還好嗎，摩妮卡？
I mean, these things happen. I mean, it's just a plate.
這種事常發生的 只不過是盤子而已
- It's not like somebody died. - It's all right. You can mourn.
-又不像是有人死了 -沒關係的，你可以哀悼的
Thank you. It was so beautiful!
謝謝你 這些本來都很漂亮的！
I'm gonna go to Joey's and get the pies.
我要去喬伊家拿幾個派
Actually, not pies. It's just pie.
事實上，不是幾個派，是一個派
I don't care.
我不在乎
Oh, my God, I've lost the will to scold.
天啊，我已經失去嘮叨的力氣了
Look, Amy..
聽著，艾美…
we got a little..
我們有一點…
a little out-of-control over there.
失去了理智
And I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
You're my sister..
你是我妹妹…
and if it really means that much to you..
如果你真的很在乎…
- So you're gonna give me the baby? - No, I was..
-那你要給我你的嬰兒了嗎？ -不，我只是…
I was gonna let you use my Ralph Lauren discount.
我只是要讓你用我的洛夫羅倫折扣
You are not gonna regret this.
你不會後悔的
- She needs changing. - No, no, no. I'll get her.
-她要換尿布了 -不，不，不，讓我去
I am super confident, totally responsible and fourth in line to raise Emma.
我超級有自信，完全有責任感 而且是扶養艾□第四順位的人
I'll be right there, Emma! Just let me get my trusty diaper bag here.
我馬上就來，艾□！ 先讓我拿一下我的尿片袋子
Well, what do you know? I guess I'll be the one who dies first.
人算不如天算 我想我將是第一個死的人
- Does Monica know about her plates? - Nope.
-摩妮卡知道瓷盤的事嗎？ -不知道
- Broke them all, huh? - Yep.
-全都打破了，是嗎？ -是的
- You gonna tell her? - Nope.
-你要告訴她嗎？ -不想
Hey. So I'm gonna put the plates back.
嘿，我要把這些盤子放回去
I think you're right. We shouldn't use these plates for a long time.
我想你是對的，我們近期內不應該 再用這些盤子
- Like only if the queen comes? - Maybe not even then.
-只有女皇來的時候才用嗎？ -或許那也不是時候
Hey. I did it.
嘿，我辦到了
I told my producer I had a family emergency. He totally bought it.
我告訴我的製作人說 我家裡發生緊急事件，他完全相信我
- Thanks for teaching me how to lie. - No problem. Next week, stealing.
-謝謝你教我如何說謊 -不用客氣，下星期教你偷竊竊
- Bye, plates. - You told her you broke all the plates?
-再見，盤子 -你告訴她你打破所有的盤子了？
What?! Something happened with the plates?
什麼？ 盤子發生什麼事了嗎？
Yeah, this raccoon came in..
是啊，一隻浣熊跑進來…